Majesty Chibuikem

Full Stack Developer

Plot 8 Barr Esom Nwankwo, New GRA Trans-Ekulu, Enugu, NG | (234) 816-619-0067 | MajestyChibuikem@gmail.com

Summary

Certified Full Stack Developer with 2+ years of experience, specializing in Web Development and Multi-platform App Development. Proficient in JavaScript, Python, SQL, Java, Python, C# and Angular. Known for enhancing software efficiency by over 20% and delivering responsive, user-friendly web solutions.

>> Work Experience <<

Full Stack Developer

World Brain Technology | Enugu, NG

8/2023 - 4/2024

- Applied new data processing systems for SQL databases that improved efficiency by over 20% and saved \$12,000.
- Mentored team members to improve company-wide JavaScript and Python knowledge. Implemented a new testing program that helped cut errors and downtime by 45%
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams to deliver on-time and on-budget projects and initiatives.

Jr Full Stack Developer

CV2Career | Enugu, NG

4/2022 - 5/2023

- Worked closely with the UX team to optimize JavaScript and Python codes, improving latency and user journey.
- Led the implementation of a new data management system, streamlining data processing and improving data accuracy by 20%.
- Introduced new security measures in SQL database reducing the risk of data theft by 20%.
- Found and repaired over 100 bugs on software systems.

>> Soft Skills <<

Time management, Creativity and Innovation, Attention to detail, Communication, Problem solving, Teamwork and Collaboration, Adaptability, Leadership, Analytical thinking and troubleshooting.

>> Hard Skills <<

➤ JavaScript, Python, Java, HTML, CSS, React and React Native, Angular, Node.js, Flask and DJango, SQL, NoSQL, MongoDB, PostgreSQL, Git, GitHub, Docker, RESTful APIs, Azure

>> Education <<

APTECH Computer Education

- Program: Advanced Diploma in Software Engineering (ADSE)
- Year Completed: 2024 (in-view)

>> Relevant Coursework <<

CS50 Computer Science Course (Harvard)

➤ Description: Followed the CS50 Computer Science course content for tutoring purposes.

>> Personal Projects <<

> Event – Management Platform

06/2024 - 08/2024

https://github.com/MajestyChibuikem/EMS.

An Platform to allow users book arenas and event centers for their events

Technologies used

Backend: Python

Database: SQLite

Frontend: CSS

> Fitness Tracking desktop

application

https://github.com/MajestyChibuikem

/FitApp

A Fitness tracking desktop application to track user progress, users can add and delete goals.

Technologies used

Backend: C#

Frontend: Windows Form

Database: Text File

Additional Features: Real-time Updates, user progress tracking, profile management